CONTACT



EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 HONG KONG POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY

• BSc (Hons) Computing

2017 - 2020 HONG KONG INSTITUTE OF VOCATIONAL EDUCATION

- Higher Diploma in Software Engineering
- GPA: 3.96 / 4.0
- Distinction Graduate

SKILLS

- React 🚳
- Tailwind CSS ~
- Next.js N
- HTML 😈
- CSS 🕫
- Javascript Js
- ASP.Net NET

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent IELTS 8.5)
- Cantonese (Fluent)
- Putonghua (Moderate)

MATTHEW FUNG

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I graduated from Hong Kong PolyU in 2024 as a Computing Major. I'm now working as a Software Engineer in Hong Kong specializing in Web Devlopment. My duties are to bring client's specifications and requirements to life using HTML and CSS. I've helped created an AI Chatbot SaaS platform using ASP.net.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Innocorn Technology

Jun 2024 - Present

Software Engineer

- Develop in-house web project for the company, ensuring quality, functionality and availability of these projects
- · Responsible for developing frontend UI for in-house projects
- Main Project: Kimiyi AI Saas Platform for AI Chatbots

Innocorn Technology

Aug 2023 - April 2024

Web Developer (Part-time)

- · Create a conversational AI chatbot using web-based technologies
- Main Project: <u>Hotel Alexandra Chatbot</u> (Deprecated)

Stemhub Holding Ltd.

Jun 2024 - Aug 2024

Web Developer (Internship)

- Research on LLM technology and create a RAG prototype
- Help conduct software testing for in-house projects
- Create an AI chatbot prototype

Zerion

Jun 2019- Dec 2019

Junior Data Analyst (Internship)

- Responsible for performing preliminary data cleansing
- Using third-party software (Kibana) to visualize data for the client
- Create a prototype for a full stack incident reporting system

REFERENCE

Daniel Lee

Innocorn Technology / CEO

Phone: +852 6673-3887